Guide to the University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees, Meeting Minutes, 1845-present UA.1.4
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minute Index, 1945-46 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- University of Pittsburgh, Copy of Budget for Minutes (1), 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- University of Pittsburgh, Copy of Budget for Minutes (2), 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 24, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, July 24, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes Index, 1946-47 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 15, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, November 15, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- University of Pittsburgh, Financial Report in Fiscal Year 1945-46, November 15, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, February 7, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, February 7, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 25, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, April 25, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 10, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, June 10, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 14, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, October 14, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 9, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, December 9, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- University of Pittsburgh, Financial Report 1946-47, December 9, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, February 27, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, February 27, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 11, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, March 11, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 12, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 8, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, June 8, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, September 21, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, September 21, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- University of Pittsburgh, Index of Minutes of Meetings, July 1948 - November 1948 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of Board of Trustees, December 14, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, December 14, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- University of Pittsburgh, Financial Report 1947-48, 1947-1948 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 8, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, March 8, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 14, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, June 14, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 19, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, July 19, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 11, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, October 11, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 13, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, December 13, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, February 27, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), February 27, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- University of Pittsburgh, Indenture of Mortgage and Deed of Trust, February 27, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), February 27, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (3), February 27, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 13, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, June 13, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- University of Pittsburgh, Index of Meeting Minutes, 1949 - 1950 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 10, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, October 10, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 18, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), December 18, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), December 18, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- University of Pittsburgh, Index of Minutes of Meetings, 1950 - 1951 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 12, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, June 12, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- University of Pittsburgh, Index of Minutes of Meetings, 1951 - 1952 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 9, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, October 9, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 18, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), March 18, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), March 18, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 15, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), June 10, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), June 10, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (3), June 10, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 14, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), October 14, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), October 14, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (3), October 14, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- University of Pittsburgh, Financial Report 1951-1952, October 14, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 9, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), December 9, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), December 9, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (3), December 9, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- University of Pittsburgh, Index of Minutes of Meetings, 1952 - 1953 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 10, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), March 10, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), March 10, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (3), March 10, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 9, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), June 9, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), June 9, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, September 18, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, September 18, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 13, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), October 13, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), October 13, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (3), October 13, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- University of Pittsburgh, Index of Minutes of Meetings, 1953 - 1954 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 8, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), December 8, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- University of Pittsburgh, Financial Report, 1952 - 1953 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), December 8, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 22, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, January 22, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 8, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), June 8, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), June 8, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (3), June 8, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 7, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, July 7, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- University of Pittsburgh, Index of Minutes of Meetings, 1954 - 1955 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 26, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), October 26, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- University of Pittsburgh, Financial Report 1953-54, October 26, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), October 26, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 14, 1954
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), December 14, 1954
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting documentation (2), December 14, 1954
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 8, 1955
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), March 8, 1955
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), March 8, 1955
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 14, 1955
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), June 14, 1955
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), June 14,1955
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 18, 1955
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, July 18, 1955
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Session of the Board of Trustees, October 21, 1955
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 29, 1955
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, November 29, 1955
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 13, 1955
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, December 13, 1955
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 22, 1955
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, December 22, 1955
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, February 14, 1956
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, February 14, 1956
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 12, 1956
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), June 12, 1956
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), June 12, 1956
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (3), June 12, 1956
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (4), June 12, 1956
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (5), June 12, 1956
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (6), June 12, 1956
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 9, 1956
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), October 9, 1956
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), October 9, 1956
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 11, 1956
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), December 11, 1956
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), December 11, 1956
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 12, 1957
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, March 12, 1957
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 11, 1957
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), June 11, 1957
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), June 11, 1957
- University of Pittsburgh, Index of Minutes of Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1957 - 1958
- University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 8, 1957
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), October 8, 1957
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), October 8, 1957
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 12, 1957
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), November 12, 1957
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), November 12, 1957
- University of Pittsburgh, Financial Report 1956-1957, November 12, 1957
- University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 10, 1957
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), December 10, 1957
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), December 10, 1957
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (3), December 10, 1957
- University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 11, 1958
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, March 11, 1958
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 10, 1958
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), June 10, 1958
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), June 10, 1958
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (3), June 10, 1958
- University of Pittsburgh, Index of Minutes of Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1958 - 1959
- University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 14, 1958
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), October 14, 1958
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), October 14, 1958
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (3), October 14, 1958
- University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 9, 1958
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (1), December 9, 1958
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation (2), December 9, 1958